<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>As it is</title>
    <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on As it is</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jgerardsimcock&#34;&gt;Simcock&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:17:43 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 12-11-2018</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:17:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</guid>
      <description>Since the UDacity course does not start until 12 December I decided to finish watching all the videos from 2nd Skies Forex. I also found a new tool; new for me at least. Trading View seems to aggregate the data feeds from a number of brokers and allows you to use their data and charting tools. Its a pretty great tool. You can even link your brokerage accounts so you can trade directly from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-08</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 15:13:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</guid>
      <description>Trading and markets have been on my mind for a very very long time. I first became very curious about trading when I read about Jim Rogers trip around the world in 2000. A few years ago I thought about trading and purchased a course from Chris Capre at 2nd Skies Forex to learn to trade. I never finished the course. I told myself I would go back and finish that course some day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Again</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</guid>
      <description>In the twilight of my temporal youth, I decideded to start over. In some ways, I feel that my life has just started.
When your mind is consumed with something, not doing/living that thing is a kind of painful dishonesty. My relationship with pain is perhaps different than most folks. I don&amp;rsquo;t like pain that leads to regrets. I welcome pain that leads to freedom, awareness and peace.
So enough bullshit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is this?</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve landed on my site.
This is an experiment. This is where I am posting updates and ideas that come to me.
Where are we? How did we get here?
I am a world citizen, currently based in Bali, Indonesia. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of my post-university years in Hawai&amp;rsquo;i and California with meaningful episodes in Beijing, NYC, Shanghai, and Bogota.
In my past, I have done many things to make a living.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>