<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>As it is</title>
    <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on As it is</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jgerardsimcock&#34;&gt;Simcock&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 18:21:48 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1: Advances in Financial Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/finml_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 18:21:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/finml_1/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 notes
Backtest fitting make Machine learning in finance more difficult than some other areas of ML
Financial ML vs standard ML
Failure of Sysphus Paradigm Discretionary PMS operate in siloed systems. Collaboration is difficult for these professionals. They have their own approaches and idiosyncratic methods for investment decision making. This approach when applied to machine learning and quantitative trading does not work. Researchers will fall into the trap of either a false positive with an overfit backtest, or the factor based approach which is a crowded strategy, but has low sharpe ratio and support in the research community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listed Volatility and Variance Derivatives</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/lvvd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 14:16:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/lvvd/</guid>
      <description>These are notes from the book Listed Volatility and Variance Derivatives by Yves Hilpisch. Additional notes are available in the notebooks at the bottom.
Chapter 1 Derivatives Volatility and Variance Volatility and Variance Concepts  Realized/Historical Volatility: Standard Deviations of log returns of financial time series Instantaneous Volatility: Volatility factor for a diffusion process Implied Volatility: volatility that if you plug into BSM model will give you the market observed price of an option If you take the square of these values you get the variance of them Annualized Variance is the result of variance times 252, the number of trading days in one year  Volatility and Variance as asset class  VIX represents 30-day variance swap VIX trading began in 2004 VIX options begain in 2006 EUREX launched futures on EUROSTOXX50 in 2005 2010 VSTOXX index options created 2014 variance futures contract for EURO Stoxx 50  Vol of Vol  VVIX, VVSTOXX reflect 30-day expectations of volatility  Volatility Trading  Long VSTOXX Future: Hedge equity positions and hedge short realized vol strategy Short VSTOXX Future: Speculate mean reversion after vol strike, reduced vega exposure to long vega option portfolios Term Structure arbitrage: If carry trade possible, and contango, short front and long back month Relative value arbitrage: Trade against other volatility instruments Long OTM Calls: Market crash insurance Short ATM Calls: Expecting mean reversion after significant market volatility Long ATM Straddle: When VVOL is high, buy put-call with same ATM strike and if vol moves fast enough in one direction, you sell  Variance Trading  Long Variance Future: Variance is higher than expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Algo Trading Notes</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/python_algo_trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:22:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/python_algo_trading/</guid>
      <description>Ito Calculus Calculus is useful for continuous process that are diferrentiable at every point from 0 to t. If your process is stochastic and has random jumps and fluctuations, you can not take the derivative of certain points along that line. For stochastic processes this is true and Ito calculua is one way to perform integration.
Reimann Sums Numerical approximation of integral with a finite sum.
Euler Discretization Discretization of continuous process and approximate numerical solution to a stochastic differential equation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Now</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 10:10:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now_2/</guid>
      <description>Here is the most recent reading list
World Affairs The Jungle Grows Back: America and the Imperiled World
The New Rules of War: Victory in the Age of Durable Disorder
Mental Hygiene Loving What Is: Four Questions That Can Change Your Life
The Abolition of Man
The Everlasting Man
Trading Listed Volatility and Variance Derivatives
Derivative Analytics with Python
Risk Dynamic Hedging
Not All Risk Mitigation is Created Equal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hayman</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/hayman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 09:53:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/hayman/</guid>
      <description>Hello Friends at Hayman Capital,
This is an inquiry aboutemail to inquire about an apprenticeship at Hayman Capital. I&amp;rsquo;ve been following the work of Hayman Capital for a few years. I am a Real Vision subscriber and as I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the interviews with Kyle Bass, I&amp;rsquo;ve only become more interested in the work the team at Hayman is doing.
My request is for consideration of a 90-day unpaid apprenticeship with Hayman Capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derivative Analytics with Python Review</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/dawp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 15:58:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/dawp/</guid>
      <description>After finishing the Real World Risk Institute I wanted to get some more knowledge about options pricing, how it works and how to do it in Python. I am grateful to Yves Hiplisch for his work on the book Derivative Analytics with Python. This is a practical and applied approach to valuing/pricing derivative instruments. The book also covers the theoretical foundations necessary to make the application of the ideas tractable. In fact, there is quite alot of mathematical notation in the text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Vision Workshop</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/real_vision_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 13:28:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/real_vision_workshop/</guid>
      <description>For the past 4 years, I have been a subscriber to Real Vision. The content and interviews have sustained my &amp;lsquo;dream&amp;rsquo; about working in financial markets. Since leaving my job to focus on the markets full time, I honestly have not had time to really watch it. However, recently, they held a live traders workshop and since I happened to be in the United States, I attended. The event took place at the Bowery Ballroom in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Thoughts from RWRI 10</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_summarary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 08:19:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_summarary/</guid>
      <description>In the closing hours of the seminar we brought it all together with some conclusions and summary. Aphorism and poetry are information compression. It seems to be Talebs natural communication style.
 The world is more fat-tailed then you think Your model has errors of 1 + alpha. That error will drastically shift your Mean and Standard Deviation more than you think. See 1. How far off is your error is 1+ alpha, 1 or 2 standard deviations?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWRI 10 Day 5</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 09:05:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_5/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: These are notes written a few days after completion of seminar. My apologies in advance for any exclusion or misapprehension of critical details. Also, to complement some of the lecture content, I&amp;rsquo;ve added related content from other sources. Bold words are links.
On the last day, class started the day with some anecdotes. In Nassim&amp;rsquo;s own words: &amp;lsquo;Verbally you cannot express your view of the world. You can be bullish and short because if you are wrong you win big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWRI 10 Day 4</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:03:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_4/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: These are notes written a few days after completion of seminar. My apologies in advance for any exclusion or misapprehension of critical details. Also, to complement some of the lecture content, I&amp;rsquo;ve added related content from other sources. Bold words are links.
On day four we discussed Extreme Value Theory, extreme prices in cryptocurrency, money laundering, cryptoassets at banks. Throughout the day we had discussions and stories bringing this into real-life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWRI 10 Day 3</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 09:06:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_3/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: These are notes written a few days after completion of seminar. My apologies in advance for any exclusion or misapprehension of critical details. Also, to complement some of the lecture content, I&amp;rsquo;ve added related content from other sources. Bold words are links.
Day 3 of RWRI 10 started with a discussion on the insurance industry and tail-risk events.
This is something I worked on Rhodium Group and it was very interesting to listen to Arie Haziza&amp;rsquo;s thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWRI 10 Day 2</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 09:00:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_2/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: These are notes written a few days after completion of seminar. My apologies in advance for any exclusion or misapprehension of critical details. Also, to complement some of the lecture content, I&amp;rsquo;ve added related content from other sources. Bold words are links.
Day 2 of RWRI 10 began with some stories about Neiderhoffer and a joke or two about the tardiness of Raphael.
First the joke: Nassim indicated that he has never seen Raphael on time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWRI 10 Day 1</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:00:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/rwri_1/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: These are notes written a few days after completion of seminar. My apologies in advance for any misapprehension of critical details. Also, to complement some of the lecture content, I&amp;rsquo;ve added related content from other sources. Bold words are links.
Today was day one of the Real World Risk Institute. The RWRI is a 5-day course of managing risks in the real world, as the name suggests. The course is led by Nassim Taleb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-02-07</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_02_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 08:24:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_02_07/</guid>
      <description>In a continuation of my efforts to develop a sense of the markets and a macro view, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to understand the main dollar pairs, treasury instruments, metals and energy futures. BTC is somehow relevant, if for nothing else, as a bellweather of extreme sentiment on current regime.
EUR/USD Daily USD/JPY 30yr T-Bond futures (Monthly) 30yr T-Bond futures (Dailt) Crude Silver Gold Copper CPER ETF with HG1 overlayed BTC DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-02-01</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_02_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 10:37:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_02_01/</guid>
      <description>I have been using TradingView to paper trade. For instruments for which TradingView does not possess a real-time data feed, you cannot paper trade. I have used some etfs as a way to expose myself to trading the futures contracts.
USD/Gold USD/Silver Palladium Platinum Dollar/Copper CEPR USD/JPY EUR/USD DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only. It is not intended to be investment advice. Seek a duly licensed professional for investment advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiva, Rumi, Cain, Abel</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/shiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 15:49:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/shiva/</guid>
      <description>In Hindu mythology, Lord Shiva, is known as the destroyer. As a westerner, my mind immediately draws up dark images of violence,chaos, and bedlam. Shiva is also a &amp;lsquo;Supreme Being that creates, protects and transforms the universe&amp;rsquo;. So clearly there is more to this idea than simply destruction.
So what is the connection? It was not obvious to me until recently and I still have not fully apprehended the significance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-27</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 14:53:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_27/</guid>
      <description>I recently implemented one of Jack Schwager&amp;rsquo;s strategies for trading. It is called wide-ranging day and takes advantage of volatility in a given instrument. It took me a while to really understand what was happening and then to implement it. I&amp;rsquo;ve posted my notebook here
I feel more and more inclined to only pay attention to a few instruments. I&amp;rsquo;d like to really understand them and see how these instruments behave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-23</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 09:23:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_23/</guid>
      <description>It looks like the dollar is strengthening against both the Euro and the Yen right now. It made me quite curious about the EuroYen relationship. I am curious to see how the EuroYen evolves over the next few months.
EUR/JPY Weekly EUR/JPY Daily USD/JPY Daily EUR/USD 4H DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only. It is not intended to be investment advice. Seek a duly licensed professional for investment advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-17</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 21:34:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_17/</guid>
      <description>Just a couple of simple ones today.
Copper 4H USDJPY USDEUR USDRUB DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only. It is not intended to be investment advice. Seek a duly licensed professional for investment advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It passes</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/letting_go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:20:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/letting_go/</guid>
      <description>On the ring, it was inscribed, &amp;lsquo;This too will pass&amp;rsquo;. So the story goes.
Yesterday a weight came down on my shoulders. It was heavy to live. I was upset about something and it was something I did not care about even a few weeks ago. It did not even exist in my world. It did not exist and then it did and then maybe it will stop existing. And when it did, I associated the thing with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-16</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:06:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_16/</guid>
      <description>Today looking at copper and oil to get a sense of metals and energy. For both we are back around levels that we saw when Trump took offfice. I don&amp;rsquo;t know it there is any relationship. The bull market that followed his arrival has completely retraced and we are back to where we started.
Copper monthly Copper daily Oil Hourly DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-11</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:16:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_11/</guid>
      <description>After having completed the work for term 1 of the Udacity Nanodegree I felt I need some more solidifiation of the ideas. I did some searching for possible trading strategies to see how they used PCA. There are many actually. I did find one that uses PCA, technical indicators and machine learning on forex. This is like the golden sweet spot for me. Here is that notebook. There is still alot of work that needs to happen on this before I am comfortable with these ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-09</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:25:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_09/</guid>
      <description>EUR/USD Still watching this as the ascending triangle is forming still and bouncing off the top of this range. I guess I should just get long and go for it.
GOLD The daily chart could convince you that there is a rounded bottom forming here over the course of the last 6 months. USD/JPY We have not really traded outside the opening level from the &amp;lsquo;flash crash&amp;rsquo; day. It looks this is a weak rally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factor Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/factor_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 19:27:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/factor_analysis/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve just completed Term 1 of Udacity&amp;rsquo;s AI for Trading Nanodegree program. This is not a review of the course content. This is a review for my own benefit of the some concepts that I need to work with and better understand. My verbal characterization of my understanding of these concepts will be crude, imprecise and potentially wrong. This is a work in progress.
Factor Models The origin of Factor Model is the French/Fama three-factor model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earning It</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/earning_it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 09:38:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/earning_it/</guid>
      <description>Are you worth it? Have you earned the privilege? Do you know how to value and protect the thing you say you value and care about? What have you given up to prove that it matters to you? What have you given to deserve it? What is the state of your mind when you interact with the thing you claim to love? Have you prepared it? Have you purified yourself in the fire?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-07</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 21:57:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_07/</guid>
      <description>One thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learned so far is that you can have the move figured out but if you don&amp;rsquo;t get in and out at the right price, you can still lose. So I&amp;rsquo;ve made the right direction calls but my entries and exits have been stopped out.
I need to go through how I intend to improve this. These images do not show my entries and exits but I have a short for the USD/JPY and a long for the USD/EUR and USD/Gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2019-01-01</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 17:13:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2019_01_01/</guid>
      <description>USD/JPY USD/XAG EUR/USD DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only. It is not intended to be investment advice. Seek a duly licensed professional for investment advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Risk</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/the_greatest_risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 14:47:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/the_greatest_risk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The greatest risk is not taking a risk&amp;rdquo;.
These words stimulated something in my mind to the question: What unknown hazards am I accepting by not taking the risks that sit in front of me? Honestly, the question certainly charged a kind of zero-fucks courage. There is not one moment when you are not facing the unknown hazards of reality. And if this truly sets in you realize you just have to go for it at all times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-28</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 20:30:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_18/</guid>
      <description>Just a few charts today. I have not taken any new positions. The ruble short trade did not go as expected. So I currently have no open positions. I am watching the following instruments for potential trades.
USD/JPY USD/TRY EUR/TRY DISCLOSURE The above references an opinion and is for information purposes only. It is not intended to be investment advice. Seek a duly licensed professional for investment advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Two Years...</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/in_two_years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 13:13:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/in_two_years/</guid>
      <description>An exercise posed today during the Udacity video.
Two years from now, where do I want to be, what do I want to be doing? Two years from now, I am trading for myself and I am very liquid with no financial doubts or concerns. I am location independent spending my time between Hawai&amp;rsquo;i, Bali, and Tokyo/Singporae/Hong Kong/NYC/London (some financial capital). Everyday I wake up and sit my morning meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trading the world</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/trading_the_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 13:41:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/trading_the_world/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I read Adventure Capitalist and Investment Biker the idea that you could use trading as way to express ideas about the world has really captivated me. Maybe that sounds like bullshit since I&amp;rsquo;ve only really started to give real attention to it. So be it. No more. Now it is true and I am living it.
The ideas that I want to express are my views about the direction of geopolitical relationships as well as the monetary relationships between nation states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You, your way, and God</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/my_way_my_path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 12:47:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/my_way_my_path/</guid>
      <description>So many systems, masters, gurus, experts, programs, classes. So many people striving, pursuing, seeking. So much human energy into this question, this pursuit. Clearly there must be answers. Maybe. Maybe the answers found, problems solved are those of the seeker. Are they your problems? If not, how can they be your answers? Do you know what you are actually after? Do you know what you actually want? Or have you just settled for someone elses desires, someone else&amp;rsquo;s problem, someone else&amp;rsquo;s narration of their solution, some one else&amp;rsquo;s system?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other people&#39;s ideas</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:44:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now/</guid>
      <description>Just dropping a quick note to share the people whose ideas I am currently consuming.
Marcos Lopez de Prado
Alexander Elder
Joseph Murphy
Chris Cole
David Goggins
Jack D Schwager
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Mark Manson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your own thoughts</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/your_own_thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:23:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/your_own_thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Agency, competence, sovereignty, independence, self-sufficiency, freedom. A bunch of words. Abstractions that point to something outside of you. Defined in some book or by some other human. Seemingly common short-cuts we use to transact with other humans and ourself. I&amp;rsquo;m concerned when I use these abstractions with myself to compel behavior. It&amp;rsquo;s actually not just these words. Its almost many words for many different behaviors and outcomes. Why do I need words and abstractions to marshall my resources to ends that I find meaningful?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of Most Resistance</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/most_resistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 21:19:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/most_resistance/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to David Goggins new book Can&amp;rsquo;t Hurt Me over and over again. There is something in the his reference to the path of most resistance and the spiritual and mental growth and abundance that lies on that path. I am sorry if that sounds like a bullshit line. But really, all abundance lies on that path. Material wealth, sure. There is also the wealth of energy and unknown that sits along that path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-11</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:17:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</guid>
      <description>Since the UDacity course does not start until 12 December I decided to finish watching all the videos from 2nd Skies Forex. I also found a new tool; new for me at least. Trading View seems to aggregate the data feeds from a number of brokers and allows you to use their data and charting tools. Its a pretty great tool. You can even link your brokerage accounts so you can trade directly from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-08</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 15:13:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</guid>
      <description>Trading and markets have been on my mind for a very very long time. I first became very curious about trading when I read about Jim Rogers trip around the world in 2000. A few years ago I thought about trading and purchased a course from Chris Capre at 2nd Skies Forex to learn to trade. I never finished the course. I told myself I would go back and finish that course some day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Again</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</guid>
      <description>In the twilight of my temporal youth, I decideded to start over. In some ways, I feel that my life has just started.
When your mind is consumed with something, not doing/living that thing is a kind of painful dishonesty. My relationship with pain is perhaps different than most folks. I don&amp;rsquo;t like pain that leads to regrets. I welcome pain that leads to freedom, awareness and peace.
So enough bullshit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is this?</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve landed on my site.
This is an experiment. This is where I am posting updates and ideas that come to me.
Where are we? How did we get here?
I am a world citizen, currently based in Bali, Indonesia. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of my post-university years in Hawai&amp;rsquo;i and California with meaningful episodes in Beijing, NYC, Shanghai, and Bogota.
In my past, I have done many things to make a living.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>