<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on As it is</title>
    <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on As it is</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jgerardsimcock&#34;&gt;Simcock&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:44:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Other people&#39;s ideas</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:44:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/reading_now/</guid>
      <description>Just dropping a quick note to share the people whose ideas I am currently consuming.
Marcos Lopez de Prado
Alexander Elder
Joseph Murphy
Chris Cole
David Goggins
Jack D Schwager
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Mark Manson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your own thoughts</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/your_own_thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 20:23:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/your_own_thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Agency, competence, sovereignty, independence, self-sufficiency, freedom. A bunch of words. Abstractions that point to something outside of you. Defined in some book or by some other human. Seemingly common short-cuts we use to transact with other humans and ourself. I&amp;rsquo;m concerned when I use these abstractions with myself to compel behavior. It&amp;rsquo;s actually not just these words. Its almost many words for many different behaviors and outcomes. Why do I need words and abstractions to marshall my resources to ends that I find meaningful?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of Most Resistance</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/most_resistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 21:19:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/most_resistance/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to David Goggins new book Can&amp;rsquo;t Hurt Me over and over again. There is something in the his reference to the path of most resistance and the spiritual and mental growth and abundance that lies on that path. I am sorry if that sounds like a bullshit line. But really, all abundance lies on that path. Material wealth, sure. There is also the wealth of energy and unknown that sits along that path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-11</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:17:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_11/</guid>
      <description>Since the UDacity course does not start until 12 December I decided to finish watching all the videos from 2nd Skies Forex. I also found a new tool; new for me at least. Trading View seems to aggregate the data feeds from a number of brokers and allows you to use their data and charting tools. Its a pretty great tool. You can even link your brokerage accounts so you can trade directly from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charts 2018-12-08</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 15:13:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/charts_2018_12_08/</guid>
      <description>Trading and markets have been on my mind for a very very long time. I first became very curious about trading when I read about Jim Rogers trip around the world in 2000. A few years ago I thought about trading and purchased a course from Chris Capre at 2nd Skies Forex to learn to trade. I never finished the course. I told myself I would go back and finish that course some day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Again</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/start_again/</guid>
      <description>In the twilight of my temporal youth, I decideded to start over. In some ways, I feel that my life has just started.
When your mind is consumed with something, not doing/living that thing is a kind of painful dishonesty. My relationship with pain is perhaps different than most folks. I don&amp;rsquo;t like pain that leads to regrets. I welcome pain that leads to freedom, awareness and peace.
So enough bullshit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is this?</title>
      <link>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:00:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jgerardsimcock.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve landed on my site.
This is an experiment. This is where I am posting updates and ideas that come to me.
Where are we? How did we get here?
I am a world citizen, currently based in Bali, Indonesia. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of my post-university years in Hawai&amp;rsquo;i and California with meaningful episodes in Beijing, NYC, Shanghai, and Bogota.
In my past, I have done many things to make a living.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>